

ABDUL WAHHAB

IT Support Officer

Work Experience

IT Officer

2018-2020

Bashir & co

IT Administrator

2016-2017

Rehan Private Limited

- Computer networks installing, configuring and maintaining computers.
- Desktop support providing direct user assistance
- Software applications working for a supplier of a software application for a specific business sector.

Contact

abdulwahhab12786@gmail.com Chathian Wala., Kasur +92321 4563480

About Me

I am an IT technical support officer who can configure computer systems, diagnose hardware and software faults and solve technical and application problems.

I can cover one or more areas of expertise, depending on the size of the organisation you work for

Qualification

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE Virtual University | 2018-2022 3.06/4 GPA

F.A

Lahore Board | 2016-2018 A Grade

MATRIC

Lahore Board | 2014-2016 A Grade

Aditional Skills

- HTML, CSS
- Java Script
- C++